

KHALID GHANI

About Me

An enthusiastic, honest and hardworking individual who is highly motivated and can work as part of a team or as an individual. Enjoy being set challenges and then overcoming them,and constantly work towards personal goals and achievements to further better skillset and experiences.



0306-3549393



khalidghani.333@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/khalidghani-1a5a45272/



House no 154 Ghulam Muhammad Goth Hub Dam Road, Karachi

LANGUAGE

- English
- Urdu
- Pashto

EXPERTISE

- Management Skills
- Microsoft office
- BookKeeping
- Problem Solving & logical
 Thinking
- Data Entry
- Customer Dealing
- 🆅 Team Work

EXPERIENCE

Mecatron solutions

Present

At Mecatron Solutions, I excel as an admin manager, overseeing daily operations with precision and also handle the logistics department, ensuring smooth import processes. Committed to efficiency and excellence in every task.

Pak Marble Factory 2020-2023

I oversaw the daily operations, ensuring smooth production and high quality results. Apart from this, I was handling sales and accounts to standardize the business

Hayat Garments 2018-2020

Managed financial health and financial responsibilities as an accountant in Hayat Garment, ensured accurate handling of expenses and liabilities. Maintained financial records and improved budget allocation for operational efficiency.

EDUCATION

GIAIC:

Cloud Applied Generative AI Engineering.

Present

Islamia Arts & Commerce College:

Intermediate in Commerce 2017-2019

Young Star Grammar School:

Matriculation in Computer Science 2015-2017

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

CSS 90%

JavaScript Typescript 85%

NextJs Tailwind CSS 85%